<!--
    ~   Copyright 2020 Liam Niehus-Staab
    ~
    ~   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
    ~   you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    ~   You may obtain a copy of the License at
    ~
    ~       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
    ~
    ~   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    ~   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
    ~   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    ~   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
    ~   limitations under the License.
    -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">partyq</string>
    <!-- PartyConnect -->
    <string name="join_party">Join Party</string>
    <string name="start_party">Start Party</string>
    <string name="partyq_logo">Party queue logo</string>

    <!-- Menu options -->
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="legal">Legal</string>
    <string name="leave_party">Leave Party</string>
    <string name="party_code">Party Code</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>

    <!-- About -->
    <string name="about_title">About partyq</string>
    <string name="about_basic_content">The partyq app lets you and a group of friends use Spotify to listen to and add music from a shared queue that only people in the party have access to. The special thing about partyq is that only one person (the host) needs to have Spotify Premium in order for everyone to be able to use it! partyq is the high-tech equivalent of passing your phone around for people to add songs to your Spotify queue.</string>
    <string name="about_tech_details_title">Technical Details</string>
    <string name="about_tech_details_content">The partyq app plays music by connecting to the Spotify app downloaded on the host’s device and simply telling Spotify to play the specific songs in the queue. This requires a Spotify Premium account because Spotify Free users can’t play specific songs; they can only play random songs by the same artist, or in the same genre as the song they really want to listen to.\n\nFor guests to perform an action, like add a song request to the queue, guests send their request to the host for them to execute on their Spotify account. All the guests connect to the host’s device via Bluetooth or wifi, so you need to be either connected to the same wifi as your host or physically within ~10 meters to be able to send and receive data as intended. This Bluetooth/wifi connection requires you to grant wifi, Bluetooth, and location privileges to the partyq app. Location privileges are unintuitively required not because partyq uses your location in any way, but because your location could potentially be obtained from data that is used to achieve a wifi device connection. Without any one of these permissions, partyq would be unable to connect your device to any others.</string>
    <string name="about_contrib_title">Contributing</string>
    <string name="about_contrib_content">The partyq app is open source under the Apache-2.0 license! That means that if you want to report an issue, contribute to the app, suggest new features, or just look at the code, you can do it all on the partyq GitHub page: <a href="https://github.com/niehusst/partyq">https://github.com/niehusst/partyq</a></string>

    <!-- Legal -->
    <string name="legal_title">Legal Information</string>
    <string name="legal_privacy_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="legal_privacy_policy_content">The partyq app does not store or share any of your Spotify data, or any other personal data. It is only used within the context of the app to perform the necessary functions and is immediately released when no longer in use.\n\nThe full partyq Privacy Policy can be found at <a href="https://github.com/niehusst/partyq/blob/main/PRIVACY.md">https://github.com/niehusst/partyq/blob/main/PRIVACY.md</a></string>
    <string name="legal_eula_content">The partyq app is legally required under the Spotify Developer Terms of Service to have all partyq users agree to an enforceable license that, in short, prohibits you from misusing the Spotify SDK used in this app and frees Spotify from any liability or warranty.\n\nThe full partyq End User License Agreement can be found at <a href="https://github.com/niehusst/partyq/blob/main/LICENSE.partyq-EULA">https://github.com/niehusst/partyq/blob/main/LICENSE.partyq-EULA</a></string>
    <string name="legal_acks_title">Open Source Acknowledgments</string>
    <string name="legal_acks_intro">Many open source tools and libraries were used in the creation of the partyq app. Below is a list of the tools used and their corresponding licenses:</string>
    <string name="legal_partyq_lic_title">The partyq License</string>
    <string name="legal_partyq_lic_content">The partyq app is also open source under the Apache-2.0 license. This means that you can see the code, and even contribute to it, via the partyq GitHub page: <a href="https://github.com/niehusst/partyq">https://github.com/niehusst/partyq</a></string>
    <string name="partyq_lic">Copyright 2020 Liam Niehus-Staab\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="spotify_api">&#8226; Spotify Web API</string>
    <string name="spotify_api_lic">https://developer.spotify.com/terms/#iii</string>
    <string name="retrofit">&#8226; Retrofit2</string>
    <string name="retrofit_lic">Copyright 2013 Square, Inc.\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="spotify_appremote_auth">&#8226; Spotify App Remote\n&#8226; Spotify Authentication Library</string>
    <string name="spotify_appremote_auth_lic">Copyright 2018 Spotify AB.\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="gps_nearby">&#8226; Google Play Services Nearby Connections API</string>
    <string name="gps_nearby_lic">Copyright 2020 Google LLC\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="timber">&#8226; Timber</string>
    <string name="timber_lic">Copyright 2013 Jake Wharton\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="glide">&#8226; Glide</string>
    <string name="glide_lic">Copyright 2014 Google, Inc. All rights reserved.\n\nRedistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:\n\n1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n\n2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY GOOGLE, INC. ``AS IS`` AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL GOOGLE, INC. OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n\nThe views and conclusions contained in the software and documentation are those of the authors and should not be interpreted as representing official policies, either expressed or implied, of Google, Inc.</string>
    <string name="android_material_espresso_samples">&#8226; Android Framework\n&#8226; Material Components for Android\n&#8226; Espresso\n&#8226; Android Architecture Components samples</string>
    <string name="android_material_espresso_samples_lic">Copyright 2018 The Android Open Source Project, Inc.\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="gson">&#8226; Gson</string>
    <string name="gson_lic">Copyright 2008 Google Inc.\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="jetbrains">&#8226; JetBrains kotlinx-coroutines\n&#8226; JetBrains kotlinx-coroutines-test\n&#8226; JetBrains kotlin-stdlib-jdk8</string>
    <string name="jetbrains_lic">Copyright 2016–2020 JetBrains s.r.o.\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="mockk">&#8226; MockK</string>
    <string name="mockk_lic">Copyright 2017 github.com/mockk\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="license_agreement">License Agreement</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="disagree">Disagree</string>
    <string name="eula">End-User License Agreement (\"Agreement\")\n\nLast updated: 2/20/21\n\nPlease read this End-User License Agreement (\"Agreement\") carefully before clicking the \"Agree\" button, downloading or using partyq (\"Application\").\n\nBy clicking the \"Agree\" button, downloading or using the Application, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Agreement put forth by the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License (\"Licensor\").\n\nIf you do not agree to the terms of this Agreement, do not click on the \"Agree\" button and do not download or use the Application.\n\n\n1. License\n\nSubject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form, with the exception of any and all Spotify intellectual property (i.e. Spotify Platform, Spotify Service, or Spotify Content).\n\n\n2. Restrictions\n\nUnder penalty of law you agree not to, and you will not permit others to:\n\n\ta) make any warranties or representations on behalf of Spotify and/or implied warranties with respect to the Spotify Platform, Spotify Service and Spotify Content, including the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement;\n\tb) modify or create derivative works based on the Spotify Platform, Spotify Service or Spotify Content;\n\tc) decompile, reverse-engineer, disassemble, or otherwise reducing the Spotify Platform, Spotify Service, or Spotify Content to source code or other human-perceivable form\n\n\n3. Limitation of Liability\n\nUNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES AND UNDER NO LEGAL THEORY, WHETHER TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), CONTRACT, OR OTHERWISE, SHALL YOU, THE INITIAL DEVELOPER, ANY OTHER CONTRIBUTOR, OR ANY DISTRIBUTOR OF COVERED SOFTWARE, OR ANY SUPPLIER OF ANY OF SUCH PARTIES, BE LIABLE TO ANY PERSON FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY CHARACTER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF GOODWILL, WORK STOPPAGE, COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION, OR ANY AN ALL OTHER COMMERCIAL DAMAGES OR LOSSES, EVEN IF SUCH PARTY SHALL HAVE BEEN INFORMED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL NOT APPLY TO LIABILITY FOR DEATH OR PERSONAL INJURY RESULTING FROM SUCH PARTY\'S NEGLIGENCE TO THE EXTENT APPLICABLE LAW PROHIBITS SUCH LIMITATION. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THIS EXCLUSION AND LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.\n\n\n4. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability\n\nWhile redistributing the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer, and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity, or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.\n\nTHE SOFTWARE (including Spotify Platform, Spotify Service and Spotify Content) IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.\n\n\n5. Modifications to Application\n\nLicensor reserves the right to modify, suspend or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Application or any service to which it connects, with or without notice and without liability to you.\n\n\n6. Term and Termination\n\nThis Agreement shall remain in effect until terminated by you or Licensor.\n\nLicensor may, in its sole discretion, at any time and for any or no reason, suspend or terminate this Agreement with or without prior notice.\n\nThis Agreement will terminate immediately, without prior notice from Licensor, in the event that you fail to comply with any provision of this Agreement. You may also terminate this Agreement by deleting the Application and all copies thereof from your mobile device or from your desktop.\n\nUpon termination of this Agreement, you shall cease all use of the Application and delete all copies of the Application from your mobile device or from your desktop.\n\n\n7. Severability\n\nIf any provision of this Agreement is held to be unenforceable or invalid, such provision will be changed and interpreted to accomplish the objectives of such provision to the greatest extent possible under applicable law and the remaining provisions will continue in full force and effect.\n\n\n8. Amendments to this Agreement\n\nLicensor reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace this Agreement at any time. If a revision is material we will provide at least 30 days\' notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.\n\n\n9. Contact Information\n\nIf you have any questions about this Agreement, please contact us at partyqhelp (at) gmail (dot) com.</string>

    <!-- Support -->
    <string name="support_title">Support</string>
    <string name="support_content">If you\'re having any issues, we\'d love to hear from you! But before that, please check out our FAQs and Common and Known Issues pages to see if you can find an answer or explanation for your problem there (it will likely also be faster, too!).</string>
    <string name="faq_link"><a href="https://github.com/niehusst/partyq/wiki/FAQs">FAQs</a></string>
    <string name="common_issues_link"><a href="https://github.com/niehusst/partyq/wiki/Common-and-Known-Issues">Common and Known Issues</a></string>
    <string name="still_having_trouble">Still having trouble?</string>
    <string name="email_developer">Email a Developer</string>

    <!-- SpotifyLogin -->
    <string name="authenticate_with_spotify">Authenticate with Spotify</string>
    <string name="info">INFO</string>
    <string name="why_is_this">Why is this?</string>
    <string name="info_content">Starting a party requires you to have the Spotify mobile app downloaded on this device and that you are logged into it with a Spotify premium account.</string>
    <string name="auth_cancelled">Authentication cancelled</string>
    <string name="no_wifi_msg">Please connect to internet to login</string>
    <string name="auth_error">Authentication failed</string>

    <!-- PartyActivity + misc -->
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="now_playing">Now Playing</string>
    <string name="queue">Queue</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="leave_confirmation_msg_guest">Are you sure you want to leave the party?</string>
    <string name="leave_confirmation_msg_host">Are you sure you want to leave the party? This will also end the party for all your guests.</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="leave">Leave</string>
    <string name="open_spotify">Open Spotify</string>
    <string name="get_spotify_free">Get Spotify Free</string>
    <string name="spotify_app_store_link">http://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.spotify.music</string>

    <!-- Search -->
    <string name="search_songs">Search songs</string>
    <string name="search_for_songs">Search for songs</string>
    <string name="add_song_to_queue">Add song to queue</string>
    <string name="no_results">No Results</string>
    <string name="error_face">Error :(</string>
    <string name="song_added_to_queue">Song Added to Queue</string>
    <string name="prev">prev</string>
    <string name="next">next</string>

    <!-- PartyCode -->
    <string name="close_popup">Close popup</string>
    <string name="your_party_code">Your Party Code</string>
    <string name="party_code_details">Share this code with friends so that they can join the party! This code can be accessed again at any time from the drop-down menu.</string>

    <!-- Queue -->
    <string name="currently_playing">Currently Playing:</string>
    <string name="no_songs_in_the_queue">No Songs in the Queue</string>
    
    <!-- NowPlaying -->
    <string name="vote_skip">Vote Skip</string>
    <string name="see_song_on_spotify_at_link">See song on Spotify at:\n%s</string>
    <string name="play_song">Play song</string>
    <string name="pause_song">Pause song</string>
    <string name="no_song_playing">No\nSong\nPlaying</string>
    <string name="skip_msg">"Your vote to skip has been counted"</string>

    <!-- PartyJoin -->
    <string name="join_content">Enter your host\'s 4-digit code to join their party.</string>
    <string name="party_code_hint">e.g. 1234</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="party_code_too_short_message">Code must be 4 digits</string>
    <string name="searching_for_party">Searching for Party…</string>
    <string name="party_not_found">Party not found</string>
    <string name="stop_searching">Stop searching</string>

    <!-- PartyEnd -->
    <string name="party_again">Party Again?</string>
    <string name="forced_end">The host has ended the party. Start or join another party to get the music flowing again!</string>
    <string name="optional_end">You\'ve now left the party. Start or join another party to get the music flowing again!</string>

    <!-- Remediation -->
    <string name="generic_error_msg">Something seems to have gone wrong connecting you to the party. Make sure that you have granted partyq all the required permissions, have downloaded the Spotify app on this device, and are logged into it with a Spotify Premium account. Please try again after checking each requirement.</string>
    <string name="denied_permissions_msg">The partyq app uses Bluetooth and/or local Wifi to connect everyone in the party and exchange data. In order to accomplish this connection, partyq requires Wifi, Bluetooth, and (unintuitively) Location permissions. Please come back after granting the missing permissions in the Settings app or by retrying your last action.</string>
    <string name="no_spotify_premium_msg">We noticed that the Spotify account logged into your Spotify app isn\'t premium. The partyq app relies on the Spotify app to play specific songs and, unfortunately, Spotify free doesn\'t let you play specific songs at will (if you tried, it would instead play a random song). Please come back after logging into a Spotify Premium account in your Spotify app.</string>
    <string name="no_spotify_msg">The partyq app relies on the Spotify app to play music; if you don\'t have the Spotify app installed (and are logged in with a premium account) then you can\'t play any music! Please come back after installing and logging into the Spotify app on this device.</string>
    <string name="spotify_crash_msg">Spotify and/or partyq\'s connections to Spotify has crashed. Without the connection to Spotify, you can\'t control what music is played. You will have to try starting the party over again, sorry!</string>
    <string name="got_it">got it</string>
    <string name="oops">OOPS!</string>
</resources>
